It's really
dangerous to be too focused on having things just right in your life.
Balance is good, and comfortability is good.
Having a firm foundation is good, having all your ducks in a row is good, obviously,
but don't be afraid to put yourself in a position of discomfort.
Don't be afraid to put yourself in a position that is maybe more vulnerable or maybe on paper it's not the smartest
decision, but you're doing so for the love of something.
You're doing so out of passion because you're chasing a dream or a vision that you have for your future.
I always tell people that you should try to live your life like a beautiful
story, okay?
And, you know,
every timeless film, every timeless novel that you can remember, they all possess
a wide spectrum of events and feelings and scenarios.
They make us feel every type of human emotion.
That's what we should be after because it's this wide spectrum of going from comfort to complete vulnerability and feeling
lost and then coming back and finding yourself again, and then this time around you have new people around you, you have newfound values, you have newfound
experience, or going from laughter and surrounded by people that make you feel good
and then going through something that puts you on a path of loneliness and isolation, but through that is where you find yourself.
Through that is where you discover a part of yourself you never knew you had, and on the other side of this, you now have a newfound love
for yourself that will propel you forward in your life through any treachery, through any hardship that you come across.
It's these types of patterns and and phases and character development is really what it is when you look at it from a bigger
picture that make a story great and that's relatable.
You know, human beings learn most from their story because we resonate with it so much, we feel these things so deeply, and so I say all
this to say don't be afraid to have an obsession for something.
Don't be afraid to push yourself to the other side of the spectrum or just do something because it's spontaneous.
Do something because you love it.
Do something because you know, not because it's, you know, the smartest decision on paper or the safest decision on paper.
You know, just simply do it because you care.
You know, through my personal development journey and trying to find my balance, trying to find my swing of things, trying to find my sweet spot
where, you know, things feel just right, you know, where I feel like all my ducks are in a row and I don't feel like I have to
pick things up and put things in order.
You know, I feel like I have total control over myself.
I feel like I have total control over the things around me.
And, you know, just things feel just right.
I've been trying to find that spot for so long.
But the longer I've tried to find it, the more I've come to realize that it doesn't exist.
It doesn't exist because that's not the nature of the life that we're supposed to live.
That's not how we're supposed to live life.
Life is supposed to be lived in phases, like waves or tides of the ocean.
They come and they go.
Some are big, some are small.
Some you flow along with ease and fluidity and some you crash into.
But that's the way it's supposed to be.
That's what creates good story.
That's what creates substance.
That's what creates room for character development.
That's the point.
That's the whole point.
And when you can adopt this type of perspective, it becomes a lot easier to not try to reject those parts of your life that feel unideal.
Now you start to see them as opportunities.
You start to see meaning and purpose in them.
And you also develop a sense of confidence and trust in yourself through this process because you learned that you got it.
You'll be fine.
The outcomes that you're scared of happening don't actually destroy you.
You realize this time and time again.
And every time you experience this, you build and build and build that trust and confidence in yourself, further enabling you to.
Continue to pursue what you love, what you have a passion for, what you crave, what you're drawn to.
And don't be afraid of coming off as weird or abnormal either, you know, like, I'm not necessarily your average
Joe, right?
Like, there's a lot of things about me that are just different in the way that I communicate.
I find it really hard to talk to people in a social setting, or at least certain types of social settings.
Whoops, don't you run away from me.
You know, and it's really hard to relate to people in environments that feel like it should be easy to.
Or I look at other people and they have just a fine time, you know, making friends and communicating and fitting in with the crowd.
I've always felt like an outsider in that regard, but instead of trying to figure out how to be somebody I'm
not and conceal this part about me,
I instead leaned into it.
And it was through that that I really found a sense of comfort in who I really am.
And that led to me empowering a lot of the interest and passions and the obsessions that I have, like liminality.
Liminality, liminal spaces is a fascination, it's an interest, it's an obsession that I have.
And it's something that I really am dedicated to.
But if I was so worried about coming off as, you know, whatever, I probably wouldn't have done that.
It wouldn't be something that I talk about publicly because it's kind of an obscure thing.
It's not mainstream or anything like that.
And it really feels like a kind of new unexplored area when it comes to talking about this type of thing in relation to psychology
and mentality and identity and those types of things, you know.
But that's what I enjoy, and that's what I really have a deep love for, so it doesn't really matter.
It doesn't really matter.
I'm going to dedicate everything I have to it.
And I know for a fact that I will find people along the way that find or share a similar fascination for it, a similar love for
it.
It's not for everybody.
It's not supposed to be.
That's why it's special.
It's not meant to be for everybody.
So whatever your passion is, whatever your idea
is, you know, let go of this expectation that everyone around you is supposed to approve of it.
You know, it's often the best ideas, the most revolutionary ideas, the most innovative ideas that are rejected the most because
they're challenging what is normal.
That's the point.
So I just wanted to have that talk because it's so important.
If you begin to live your life, if you begin to perceive your life in this manner, I truly believe that you will be much more
fulfilled than just trying to have it all right all the time, you know what I mean?
I do have a little surprise for you guys.
I got, I got a new car.
I upgraded from the 2007 Honda Accord.
I love that thing.
Um, took me on several road trips.
It was loyal.
It was, man, I feel like I'm cheating on her.
Dang, no, she, uh, she was a loyal one, and I miss her dearly.
But she was starting to have some problems.
She was starting to have some problems, and so I upgraded.
I want to show you guys my new car, my new little toy.
I'll show you guys the exterior in a minute here, but this is a Cadillac Lyric V. Has a ton of cool
features like massage seats, as you can see here, heated seats, ventilated seats, amazing stereo
system.
If you look here, I don't know if you guys can see that, but there are speakers in the headrest.
Very spacious, big glass roof.
This thing is absolutely beautiful.
Has a V mode which is, oh my gosh, this thing is unbelievably fast.
But nonetheless, I'll show you guys the exterior really quick.
All right, here we go.
So when you turn this thing on, does a cool little light show in the front.
It didn't do it, whatever, anticlimactic.
I promise you, a little Cadillac logo in the front there, very cool feature.
I love these wheels.
These came with the car.
This thing looks so, so futuristic.
I just love it, man.
I just love it.
This is definitely an upgrade from what I came from.
The illuminated door handles.
Nonetheless, this thing's awesome.
You know, for those of You that know a bit about my story, a bit about my
journey, to go from where I started to the position that I'm in now, it didn't take for me to act perfectly.
It didn't take for me to do it all right or have, you know, everything in the right place at all times in order to make that type
of transformation.
In fact, it's pretty, a lot quite the opposite.
You know, it's exploring myself, it's testing my limits, it's putting myself into situations that, again, maybe aren't the smartest on paper, but I have a belief
in myself.
I have a belief in my capability and I'm going to pursue that.
And that leads you to do things that people will question because it's not normal because most people don't do these types of things.
You know what I mean?
I honestly think that one of my greatest strengths along my entire journey has been my willingness
to face whatever outcome arises in the event of me pursuing what I love or have a passion for or an interest in
or have a belief in with an honest
intent, a sincere intent to just explore that and throw myself into it, you know, and do it fully and not, and not hold
back, you know, not be fearful of whatever outcome may be because I just know that that that's the way it's supposed to be, you know.
I think everything happens for a reason and I trust that I can can handle whatever outcome arises.
I truly do, and so that just leads to progression, that leads to self-discovery, self-development, character development, and if you me a wonderful
story.
So I absolutely love you guys, man.
Um, I really think that this is one of the greatest, most important life lessons that I've learned in my own personal journey.
So I'm more than happy to share it with you guys.
I absolutely love you.
Um, I appreciate your time and I will see you soon.